.
All right, rich boy, there you go.
Come on.
Next.
.
Look who it is.
How you free us!
You're the one that should be in here!
.
They just locked you up, you freak!
Get off me!
Hey, Kent, it's me, Eric.
Struck by lightning lately?
.
Good to see you, Clark.
Tell my two favorite ex-girlfriends I said hello.
Keep moving, Ian.
Jeez, kid, you seem to know a lot of people in here.
Where's Lex?
Got ten minutes.
.
Hey, Luke!
What are you doing here, my friend?
Huh?
I'm gonna take you back to your room, okay?
Just relax.
Oh!
He doesn't belong in there. He's being drugged.
Well, we don't know that for sure.
This isn't his first brush
with mental illness.
Lionel's never gonna let him out.
I'm his only chance.
Clark,
you can't just break somebody out
of a state institution.
Then you would go to jail and Lex would be
out there a fugitive with your secret
on the tip of his tongue.
Pete knows my secret and that's turned out okay?
Lex is different.
Look,
Clark, I'm not saying that you should put your secret
above Lex's well being, I just
think that you should stay out of this one, that's all.
Dad...
Clark!
You don't know everything that's going
on.
Now, if you get involved, it could just get worse.
You know, you've got another friend in a hospital
that you haven't visited.
Lana doesn't really want to see me right now.
She was in shock, Clark. She didn't mean what she said.
Except she's right. All I've done is put her in danger.
She's better off without me.
What about you? Are you better off?
You know, you can save the whole world, Clark,
but you've got to take care of your own heart, too.
Go see her.
Good, Lana. One more step.
Okay. Okay, that's enough for today.
It goes for you, too, Adam.
I know my limits.
If you overdo it, you'll undo all your hard work.
If I listened to people like you, I'd still be in bed.
Good work today, sweetie.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, Lana.
I'm sorry.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Like you wouldn't believe.
I think you're getting off way too easily.
Excuse me?
You have to learn to push through the pain.
We all sat down every time it hurt.
This country never would have been built.
Well, I doubt the Founding Fathers broke their legs in four places.
What happened? Bad pilot for cheerleading practice?
No, no, no, seriously.
How'd you end up in here?
Or Scott spooked.
He ended up under its hooves.
Hmm. I'm guessing that's not a good place to be.
Madam.
Lana.
All right, Lana.
We both know that you have one more lap in you and this puppy.
Let's see it.
How about not?
I know struggle is probably not in your vocabulary,
but just to let you know, here it's credo.
For your information, I haven't walked in a month.
Feeling sorry for yourself may work now,
but it's not gonna get you up a flight of stairs, is it?
Are you always this obnoxious?
I'm just telling you how it is.
No one's ever honest with girls like you.
Bet you have a boyfriend that's always protecting you, right?
But he's not here.
No one's gonna fight this battle for you.
You're on your own. See you around.
Bye.
Good luck.
You too.
Thank you.
Bye.
Bye, Lana.
You were making such good progress, son.
You're the one who taught me.
Attack adversity head on.
And had you been taking your medication, you would have done just that.
This institution is not your adversary, Lex.
Your illness is the enemy.
But I'm better now.
I don't need the meds.
That story about you killing your parents,
there's nothing more than a paranoid delusion.
See, somewhere along the line, I veered off into the abyss,
but I've managed to claw my way back.
But that's irrelevant now.
What do you mean?
When your attempt to escape failed,
you sabotaged it.
I wished my efforts to have you released
to be cared for at home.
But I told you.
I'm cured.
A cured patient doesn't belong in a hospital.
Oh, it's painful to see you like this.
I'm sorry.
I fell out.
I fell out with her.
Mom.
Don't you try
to killed your sister and dad.
And neither did I so you don't want to kill me.
You'reие trying to pull paint with a plastic đónh me.
Dost you need paint as you doering?
You душyou, rever,
if you want a deadセur sungym taro,
isn't not paint as sy.
The water's insane!
You did this to me!
Well, if it isn't Ku Klux Van.
Get out of my grill, freaks.
I'd watch your mouth in here if I were you.
Yeah, we heard about your little one-man ethnic cleansing campaign.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come on.
You were out there picking off meteor freaks like ducks on the first day of hunting season.
And now you're stuck in here with all us ducks.
Quack, quack.
We don't want to hurt you, Van.
Believe it or not, the three of us have something in common.
I seriously doubt that.
Clark Kent put us all in here.
And word on the ward is you know his weakness.
Why should I tell you?
Oh, because we're looking to sample the sweet taste of revenge.
See, if you weaken him, I can leech his powers and break us all out of here.
Wait, you took Clark's powers.
How?
It's a lightning strike.
You took him back with a high voltage shock.
How do I know I can trust you freaks?
The enemy of your enemy is your friend.
I don't feel comfortable moving forward with the procedure yet.
Comfortable?
Your comfort level is of no concern to me, Doctor.
I've indulged you for a month while you've conducted this drug therapy of yours.
And not only does Lex's memory remain completely intact, but he attempted to escape.
I can't afford to waste any more time.
Mr. Luther, the procedure you're proposing is draconian.
It's successful in less than 50% of patients.
And it's not just for the patients.
It's for the patients.
I'm sorry.
And it leaves the other half with irreparable brain damage.
Are you really willing to take that risk?
No risk, no reward.
Isn't that what they say, Doctor?
Performing this procedure on a patient who does not require it is unconscionable.
But it's not the first time.
You've experimented with it before.
We had a mutual agreement, didn't we?
I strongly suggest you keep your part of the bargain.
So start the procedure immediately.
Clark, turn the light on.
It's bad for your eyes.
What are you doing burning the midnight oil?
Trying to prove Lex doesn't belong in Belle Reve.
And what'd you find on Lex?
Well, I have his medical records.
Dr. Foster is definitely drugging him.
Clark, there are millions of reasons why she could be administering this drug.
Psychotherapy is just trial and error.
This doesn't prove anything.
I know.
But I gotta do something.
Well, why don't we work on this in the morning, okay?
This is a very important task.
This is just a pit stop.
I have to pick up Lana on my way home.
How is Lana?
It's been really tough.
She could use some moral support.
I sent her a card.
Nothing says I love you more than a $1.50 piece of cardboard.
If she wanted me there, Chloe, I'd be there.
Right now, I'm just trying to keep my promises for once.
Wait, I know she will know about I love you, too.
Watch your member.
Don't pressure her.
This is your life and what she lives.
Now, I feel like I should do a thing for her.
Two times you want to see her does that make all the same?
Oh, yeah.
When I'm out, your job still Damn right is to save my life...
Between this and getting high.
But you can't think we can really change her, right?
You know, everyone wants to survive.
You know I would personally leave her to a few children's fox eggs.
You know what?
Let alone don'tなん could get you by mom's shoulder.
You know, she might just want you and Mom so dearly,
Of course.
Is that my package?
Mm-hmm.
Still don't get what you want with one of these rocks.
How about we just forget the whole thing?
Why do we float your boat, my man?
I don't know.
Hmm.
So did you get what you were waiting for?
It's in the box.
Ken comes back, he's gonna have a little surprise waiting for him.
He's like...
You need a spot?
Look, when Clark shows up, I'll be ready.
But until then, let's not pretend like we're friends.
I just wanted you to meet my better half.
Well, you should know better than to trust a meteor freak.
What's the emergency?
Everything's fine here.
Is this what you're planning on doing to Lex?
There's nothing wrong with Lex. You've been drugging him.
That's why he's having paranoid delusions.
If you're here to accuse me of criminal malpractice,
I hope you have the facts to back it up.
I'm sure you could talk your way out of Lex's dubious drug regime.
But what about the existing lawsuit for radical electroshock therapy?
What happened to Mr. Watkins was unfortunate.
But for your information, that suit was dropped.
Because Lionel Luther paid it off.
I'm very busy.
So if you two will excuse me.
Do you think if you turn Lex into a vegetable that Lionel Luther's gonna let you off the hook?
You have all the power here, Doctor.
Please, help Lex and yourself.
Newspaper, magazine, crossword puzzle.
What do you think?
Right.
Must be a little bit difficult to turn the pages.
What do you do when you have an itch?
Get out of my face.
Boy, I bet you were just itching to get out of this place.
Mr. Luther, what would you do if I told you I'd figured out a way for certain animals to escape the zoo?
I'd ask you why you're still here.
Funding issues.
Once I'm out, I need to disappear.
And a new identity doesn't come cheap.
Oh, I admired your ambition.
But when you tried to murder my friends to get my money,
you went a little too far.
I know I've made some mistakes in the past.
But I'm all better now.
And I'm happy for you.
The both of you.
Now, take your little card and go sucker some other patient with a bank account.
Suit yourself.
Of course, if my brain were about to be deep fried, I might have a little bit different attitude.
It's gonna be hard to get around when your toes are permanently curled.
Fear's an effective sales tactic, but it doesn't work on me.
How about facts?
See?
You're on deck, Mr. Luther.
Where'd you get this?
I know everything that goes on in this dump.
If you want to save your cerebrum, you know where to find me.
I'll26
Wow, that was fast.
There we go.
Let me press this.
Hey.
Dr. Snobo, honey.
Nothing, as you can see.
Dr. concluded your threat.
Thank you, Dr. Fudge.
Yes?
As you've just said,
I see you changed your therapy time.
Yeah, I wasn't crazy about the company.
Would you believe me if I told you I was a nice guy once?
With no issues?
Nice guys normally have the most issues.
That's why I came.
I wanted to apologize.
Sorry for taking it out on you.
I was upset because you're kind of right.
I haven't really been pushing myself.
And I guess it's because I know that when I get back on my feet,
my life's going to be different.
I don't really know if I'm ready to face it.
So you never got around to telling me why you're in here.
Isn't it obvious?
Fine cuisine, postmodern decor.
No, really, what happened?
Well, uh, I tried to get into a burning building
and a beam collapsed on me.
My parents were inside.
I thought I could save them.
God, I am so sorry.
It happened.
Now I have to move on.
See?
Guess I'm a little afraid of my future, too.
I'm sorry.
And I convinced Foster to stop
the construction.
She's on her way right now to sign the cancellation papers.
And you think this is a good thing?
Clark, he knows your secret.
I can't let him turn Lex into a vegetable just for that.
You can't trust him.
And you've never given him a chance.
And you give him too many.
You think it's easy keeping a lid on your secret?
I've got to think about it every time we're around other people
to make sure I don't slip.
I've got to remember to say meteor rock instead of kryptonite.
And I always got to cover your underpants,
explain exits.
Pete, I'm sorry.
You've never said anything.
Clark, that's not the point.
The point is that I got your back.
But Lex won't.
Chloe, what's wrong?
Claire Foster's dead.
They found her car wrapped around a tree off Highway 54.
I feel the invisible hand of Lionel Luther.
You two had better back off before he
sets his sights on you.
Now, I know you were just trying to help Lex,
but I think you've made matters worse.
Now, there's got to be another way to stop the procedure.
Clark, Dr. Foster tried to stop it,
and look what happened to her.
Lionel Luther is going to make sure this procedure happens.
Lex.
Clark, I knew you'd come.
Let's get you out of here.
All this time, I was right about you.
What do you know?
It worked.
If it weren't for you, Kent, I'd be at Harvard right now
with a co-ed on each arm.
What the hell are you doing to him?
I'm going to kill him.
Your buddy's our first class ticket out of here.
You planned an escape.
I'm not giving you a cent.
Clark's my friend.
Well, you ought to pick your friends better,
considering he didn't tell you his little secret.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
No.
Lex.
Leave him alone.
Or you'll do what?
Mr. Luther.
Considering they're coming to fry your ass in about five minutes.
Leave him alone!
Well, here he is.
Right on schedule.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
There he is.
Time to give me those powers back.
It's not like you use them anyway.
This will never work.
Are you kidding?
There's enough voltage in here to power a small third world
country.
Save your strength, Clark.
I'm going to need it.
Oh, my god.
Clark!
You got Clark!
Help me get out!
No!
I don't know, but I ain't taking any chances.
No! No!
There you go. Almost.
Okay.
Done.
It's not Mount Everest,
but it is a start.
A few days ago, I wouldn't have even thought
that was possible.
Sometimes you just have to look at possibilities
straight in the eye.
Mrs. Kent.
What a surprise. Chloe had a late deadline.
She asked if I could give you a ride home.
I'm gonna go.
Okay. Hello.
Hello.
Interesting physical therapist.
So, how's Clark?
I got his card.
I'm sorry he hasn't come by to see you.
To be honest,
that was kind of my idea.
Lana, I know that Clark
is not always the easiest person to understand,
but he never meant to put you in danger.
Did they send you to argue his case?
He doesn't know I'm here.
I'm sure he'd be upset that I was meddling.
I just want him to be happy.
I know.
But you need to be happy, too, Lana.
Thanks, Mrs. Kent.
I'm sorry.
Please.
I'll pay you whatever you want.
You'll never have to work another day in your life.
He doesn't want your money, son.
He wants to make you better
Just like I do
You're a liar
No, be strong, Lex
I'm sorry, son
Don't do this to us
Be strong
I'm sorry, son
I didn't think it would have to come to this
If it were a gangrenous limb
We could amputate
But the brain
Unfortunately
Is infinitely more complex
Do it
Hey
Come on, let's go
I'm right here
What happened? You better half
It's a lot easier to break one person out than two
Let's go
What is it? What's happening?
We don't have any power
There must be a short somewhere
Well, fix it
Everyone else, please
This is fine
Pre-con إün
You take the spray
And the
You take the excrement
Dad
Let me go
She doesn't love you
You told them
That you want America
What about us?
You can make
Welcome back to being normal, Clark.
Kind of sucks, doesn't it?
All right, farm boy, you're gonna pay
for the two wasted years I spent in here.
Eric, let's go.
I'm not through with him yet.
They're gonna realize we're gone.
They're gonna be here any minute.
What do I care? It's not my problem.
No, no, no, wait a second.
We're a team. I thought we were friends.
There's no such thing as friends in here.
Hey!
Is that all you got?
That little jolt make you insane, Clark?
Who's afraid to use their powers?
No.
I don't know what happened.
Again.
But sir, the way this equipment is working, we should wait.
Do it.
Again.
Tell me where Lex is. Now.
Lex.
Sir.
It's over.
Hi.
Hey.
Am I hallucinating? No crutches?
Well, it's pretty amazing what you can accomplish when someone's cracking a wick over your head.
You okay?
Yeah.
This don't look that spooky.
I tend to get dehydrated from time to time.
Well, I know that these probably can't compare to the desserts in here,
but I, um, I wanted to thank you for being such a pain in the butt.
Anytime.
So I guess this is goodbye.
Just because I'm finished physical therapy doesn't mean I won't combine.
Lana, please.
I'm a memory from a painful moment in your life.
Who wants to be reminded of that?
We all push through the pain, Adam.
Maybe you're not willing to do that.
Lana, I'll be completely honest with you.
I like you.
But I get the feeling that there's someone else.
And I don't want to be caught in the middle of anything.
There is nothing to be caught in the middle of, but I'm not really ready to be jumping into another relationship right away.
Trust me, I don't want to be a rebound boy either.
But I would like to be a friend.
Oh, I'd like that.
Good.
Then we're friends.
Yeah.
Friends.
Lex.
Clark.
How you feeling?
Great, actually.
Never better.
I heard you came to visit me, and I wasn't a very cordial host.
If that's true, I'm sorry.
Did your dad tell you why he had you committed?
He said I had a psychotic break.
I think my island trauma precipitated it.
I'm just grateful my father recognized it in time.
Me too.
Do you want to tell me something, Clark?
No.
It's good to have you back, Lex.
Welcome home.
You know, Clark, there is one thing I'll never forget.
What's that?
That's one of the things I once wished for.
How important your friendship is to me.
Lex is OK.
Your secret's safe.
You got to find some consolation in that.
Lex is right.
Lionel got away with murder.
But you didn't tell him what really happened.
I figured, what's the point?
Clark.
Clark, I do not want you and Chloe taking up this charge.
Someone's going to make Lionel pay for his crime.
Someday, somebody is going to make Lionel pay for his crime.
But that day is not today, Clark.
I know this is very difficult for you,
but you have to realize that there are people out there who
are more powerful than you are.
You've given me an answer.
Lex?
Hey, выпусك
You OK?
In a way, I envy Lex.
You seem so happy.
I wish I could erase the last few months of my life.
I heard they're having a welcome back party for Lana at the Talon.
Why don't you go?
You never quit, do you?
It's called tough love.
Come on, go.
Why didn't you show me this sooner?
We've been working all week to enhance the audio, sir.
A week? And this is the best you can do?
We have a man waiting for aarsi to stop his date.
Who is it?
She'll be here any minute.
I wish I could protect her.
Run off.
The only thing we can do is save the girl's arm.
Rather than this...
I'll make you leave.
Tanaka tells the Houston converts markets are...
And all the mistakes one life can take
They all finally start to go away
And now that we're here, it's all far away
And I feel like I can face the day
And all the mistakes one life can take
They all finally start to go away
And now that we're here, it's all far away
And I feel like I can face the day
And I can forgive, and I'm not ashamed
To be the person that I am today